sobadsogood.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy | So Bad So Good

## Your Privacy

**Your Data**  
We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.

Our systems are not designed to associate personal information with your activities (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, email, address or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information.

Our systems are designed to retain log data for up to 7 days after it is collected. We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account.

We don't share your personal data with other companies. We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies.

**Your Location**  
We collect or share your location only with permission. In serving you, we may use or store your precise geographic location, if you give us permission to do so. We do not use or share this data for any other purpose. Many devices will indicate through an icon when location services are operating. We only share this location information with others as approved by you.

**Ad Tracking**  
Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customise content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity.

**Your Privacy**  
You can ask privacy questions. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: editorial@sobadsogood.com

**3rd Party Sites**  
Service providers access data on our behalf. In order to serve you, we may share your personal and anonymous information with other companies, including vendors and contractors. Their use of information is limited to these purposes, and subject to agreements that require them to keep the information confidential. Our vendors provide assurance that they take reasonable steps to safeguard the data they hold on our behalf, although data security cannot be guaranteed. Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

**Security**  
We take steps to protect personal information We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

**Timeframe**  
This privacy policy was last updated on Feb 28th 2015. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.

## Copyright

**DMCA Policy**  
So Bad So Good Pty Ltd ("Company") has adopted the following policy toward copyright infringement in accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (http://lcweb.loc.gov/copyright/legislation/dmca.pdf). The address of the Designated Agent to Receive Notification of Claimed Infringement ("Designated Agent") is listed at the end of this policy.

SO BAD SO GOOD PTY LTD ­ DMCA COPYRIGHT POLICY

Reporting Copyright Infringement:

If you allege that your intellectual property is being violated, you must submit to the Company:

A physical or electronic signature of a person authorised to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright that has been allegedly infringed;

Identification of the works or materials being infringed;

Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing including information regarding the specific location of the infringing materials on the Company’s website that the copyright owner seeks to have removed, with sufficient detail so that Company is capable of finding and verifying its existence;

Contact information of the person notifying the Company, including address, telephone number and, if available, e­mail address;

A statement that the notifier has a good faith belief that the material is not authorised by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and a statement made under penalty of perjury that the information provided is accurate and the notifying party is authorised to make the complaint on behalf of the copyright owner.

Once Proper Bona Fide Infringement Notification is Received by the Designated Agent:

It is Company's policy:

To remove or disable access to the infringing material;

To notify the content provider, member or user that it has removed or disabled access to the material; and that repeat offenders will have the infringing material removed from the system and that Company will terminate such content provider's, member's or user's access to the service.

Procedure to Supply a Counter­Notice to the Designated Agent:

A physical or electronic signature of the content provider, member or user;

Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or disabled;

A statement that the content provider, member or user has a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or a misidentification of the material; and Content provider's, member's or user's name, address, telephone number, and, if available, e­mail address and a statement that such person or entity consents to the jurisdiction of the Federal Court for the judicial district in which the content provider's, member's or user's address is located, or if the content provider's, member's or user's address is located outside the United States, for any judicial district in which Company is located, and that such person or entity will accept service of process from the person who provided notification of the alleged infringement.

If a counter­notice is received by the Designated Agent, Company may send a copy of the counter­notice to the original complaining party informing that person that it may replace the removed material or cease disabling it in 10 business days. Unless the copyright owner files an action seeking a court order against the content provider, member or user, the removed material may be replaced or access to it restored in 10 to 14 business days or more after receipt of the counter­notice, at Company's discretion.

Please contact the Designated Agent to Receive Notification of Claimed Infringement for Company at dmca@sobadsogood.com or at:

So Bad So Good Pty Ltd  
Attn: Sobadsogood.com - Copyright Agent  
Unit 8 77 Bourke Road, Alexandria  
Sydney, NSW 2015
